{
    "problem": "x0=?",

    "choice1": "1",
    "choice2": "2",
    "choice3": "3",
    "choice4": "4",
    "correctanswer": "1"
},
{
    "problem": "x1=?",

    "choice1": "1",
    "choice2": "x",
    "choice3": "1/x",
    "choice4": "0",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "x-m=?",

    "choice1": "mx",
    "choice2": "1/mx",
    "choice3": "1/xm",
    "choice4": "0",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "(x2*x4)3=?",

    "choice1": "x11",
    "choice2": "x24",
    "choice3": "x9",
    "choice4": "x18",
    "correctanswer": "4"
},
{
    "problem": "(a6b4)1/2=?",

    "choice1": "ab3",
    "choice2": "a2b3",
    "choice3": "a3b2",
    "choice4": "ab2",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "If a=2,b=3 then a+b=?",

    "choice1": "1",
    "choice2": "3",
    "choice3": "4",
    "choice4": "5",
    "correctanswer": "4"
},
{
    "problem": "If a=2,b=-3 then 4a+b=?",

    "choice1": "2",
    "choice2": "1",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "4",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},
{
    "problem": "If p=4,q=-3 then 2(p2+q)=?",

    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "26",
    "choice3": "20",
    "choice4": "15",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "If a=3,b=-2 then a2+6/b=?",

    "choice1": "1",
    "choice2": "6",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "10",
    "correctanswer": "2"
},
{
    "problem": "If a=1.5,b=-4,c=1.8 then 4ab+10c=?",

    "choice1": "10",
    "choice2": "6",
    "choice3": "-6",
    "choice4": "16",
    "correctanswer": "3"
},